# DEEPESH MISHRA (1) Featured

Senior Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development Life Cycle, Software Design, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Requirement Analysis, Incident Resolution, Documentation, Software Integration, Bug Fixing, Client Engagement



Current Location: Gurgaon Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Gurgaon, Delhi / NCR Notice Period: 15 Days or less Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development Life Cycle, Software Design, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Requirement Analysis, Incident Resolution, Documentation, Software Integration, Bug

Fixing, Client Engagement

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

### Summary

Competent Professional with 9 years of experience in building software solutions by studying information needs, conferring with users, studying systems flow, data usage, and work processes

Successfully coded, implemented and integrated complex software programs using Java - Core, Swing, Collection Framework, Multithreading and Linux, Shell Scripting

Led the design, development, testing and implementation of a web-based application technologies including Java Possess considerable experience of 4 years of experience in Telecom industry

Understanding business objectives and developing solutions using analytics, automation and machine learning / Al techniques for customer success and metrics to track progress

Skilled in:

Report automation based on log extraction by using - Core Java & Linux

OSS, fetch and extract logs from nodes

Apache - POI, Commons and iText Libraries

Steered software integration and deployment on UAT & Production servers of various Nationalized Banks in India

## **Work Experience**

Wipro Technologies Pvt. Ltd as Senior Software Engineer Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

Ericsson India Global Services Pvt. Ltd as Engineer Jul 2015 to Jul 2019

Syscom Corporation (Smart Chip Limited), as Software Engineer Jan 2011 to Jul 2015

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Not Specified) from C.S.J.M University, Kanpur (U.P.), India in 2008

PG: MCA (Computers) from U.P. Technical University, Lucknow (U.P.), India in 2011

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Tomcat	
MySql, SQL Server 2008 R2	
PostgreSQL	
Hibernate	
Python, C#.net	

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

### **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time